[{"answer": "Genera", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " 1Tech Laboratories.  This is Nancy speaking", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Genera", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Nancy, hi.  This is Bob from Grand Technical Products.  Im calling in regards t", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": " 1Tech Laboratories.  This is Nancy speaking", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " OK.  Let me look that up for you.  Do you have an order number", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Nancy, hi.  This is Bob from Grand Technical Products.  Im calling in regards t", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yes.  Its 151-58-9984", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 21, "question": " OK.  Let me look that up for you.  Do you have an order number", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " All right.  I see you placed an order for 100 of the basic microscope kits", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Yes.  Its 151-58-9984", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Thats right.  But, weve gotten some new requests for those and I was wonderin", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " All right.  I see you placed an order for 100 of the basic microscope kits", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Lets see.  The order hasnt shipped out yet, so that should be OK.  Ill add 10", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Thats right.  But, weve gotten some new requests for those and I was wonderin", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Great.  Thank you", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Lets see.  The order hasnt shipped out yet, so that should be OK.  Ill add 10", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Sure.  Youre new total will be $4322.  Since youve ordered 200 now, youv", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Great.  Thank you", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Oh, thats good news", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Sure.  Youre new total will be $4322.  Since youve ordered 200 now, youv", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " You should receive those in about 15 days", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, thats good news", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Thanks, Nancy", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 41, "question": " You should receive those in about 15 days", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Good-bye", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Thanks, Nancy", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": "Leaving a Messag", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Youre welcome.  Good-bye", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Hi.  Youve reached Patrice William at Walter Financial Group.  I", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Leaving a Messag", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Hi Patrice.  This is Larry from Conway Advertising.  Im missing a few pages o", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Hi.  Youve reached Patrice William at Walter Financial Group.  I", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Hi.  Youve reached the desk of Larry Conway.  Please leave ", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Hi Patrice.  This is Larry from Conway Advertising.  Im missing a few pages o", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Hey Larry.  This is Patrice from Walter Financial Group returning your call.  I", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Hi.  Youve reached the desk of Larry Conway.  Please leave ", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": "0.  Feel free t", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Hey Larry.  This is Patrice from Walter Financial Group returning your call.  I", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": "Wrong Numbe", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 76, "question": "0.  Feel free t", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Lewis  & Associates.  Can I help you", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Wrong Numbe", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Hi.  Can I speak with Ken Rogers, please", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Lewis  & Associates.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Who are you trying to reach", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Hi.  Can I speak with Ken Rogers, please", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": "Ken Rogers", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Who are you trying to reach", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Im sorry.  You have the wrong number", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Ken Rogers", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Is this 252-6634", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Im sorry.  You have the wrong number", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " No, its 252-6635", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Is this 252-6634", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Oh, my apologies. I must have misdialed", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " No, its 252-6635", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " No problem", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Oh, my apologies. I must have misdialed", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": "Appointmen", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " No problem", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": "Suzanne Jenkins office", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Appointmen", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Hi.  Could I speak to Ms. Jenkin please", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Suzanne Jenkins office", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " May I ask what your call is regarding", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Hi.  Could I speak to Ms. Jenkin please", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " I need to make an appointment with her", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " May I ask what your call is regarding", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " OK.  I keep her calendar.  I can do that for you", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 101, "question": " I need to make an appointment with her", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Oh, all right.  Id like to meet with her next week about a project Im working o", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 102, "question": " OK.  I keep her calendar.  I can do that for you", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Shes free on Monday at 10 a.m.  Does that work for you", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 106, "question": " Oh, all right.  Id like to meet with her next week about a project Im working o", "qSentId": 105},{"answer": " Sure.  Thats fine.  My name is Carol Whitley", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 107, "question": " Shes free on Monday at 10 a.m.  Does that work for you", "qSentId": 106},{"answer": " And your phone number", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 108, "question": " Sure.  Thats fine.  My name is Carol Whitley", "qSentId": 107},{"answer": "Its 652-854-621", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 112, "question": " And your phone number", "qSentId": 111},{"answer": " OK.  Ive got you down for 10 a.m. on Monday the 23rd", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Its 652-854-621", "qSentId": 112},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 114, "question": " OK.  Ive got you down for 10 a.m. on Monday the 23rd", "qSentId": 113},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "02-01", "aSentId": 115, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 114}]
